sup everyone
tamers1545 here with a very special
video today it's a brand new year so you
know what that means it's a brand new
video
ah reba we're having a fiesta
so today i'm gonna show you how to make
the official and that's right official
sock underground fiesta tacos up in this
first we're gonna need a taco
you can get this at anywhere i got mom
from doll daniel and and
sonic as you can see he represents a
play he's not going to be a food item in
this so be warned about that he is the
play he is the foundation that holds all
this food together a lot like
how it a lot like how his name is in the
title but matt's not stock's not going
to be alone for very long no uh because
we got so we got his bro we got some
green jello up in this it's like
jiggly like max ass and one
thing i love about you that i love your
donut is that you can cut it into
squares and if you do that it makes it
much much easier to handle look at that
you got like that's like the perfect
size for a taco for a fiesta taco if you
know what i mean
so we're gonna put that there max ass
like a bag of marinara sauce
now we're not done with this taco no not
not yet we're gonna need
we're gonna need some cheese up in this
and
of course you know what this represents
we all know what this represents
this is the one the only
barbie montclair of the dresden
household
and we're not done yet this is like a
dessert
taco as you can see with the cheese and
the jello so we're gonna need we're
gonna need a little bit of mindy to
sweeten this up so i got some peach
jelly right here
put that on it's like it's like mindy
just pooped all over the place
that's so funny
and this this taco is basically done oh
oh no i forgot we got some creamed
corn to go with this because it's the
dessert one i just gotta drain some of
the
black corn first
like liquid
that that's good enough
and then just sprinkle it on there
damn i'm ready to dive in right now
damn i think i'll do it
oh my god
that's good
although
i think i'm ready to move on from the
appetizer how about you guys
we're gonna need a bigger plate
gotta get another one of these this is
the main course one of course ram
this is what i like to call
the big
and who do you call when you need the
big we call mag the hedgehog up in
this again that boy just can't
stay down
adding on to the main course we're gonna
add some of this
tangy yellow mustard
after that
we can we can leave our boy knuckles out
of this
we gain all the boys in this
come on boys
and this is what i consider
the main taco that was the dessert
this is the main deal this is why
you know i'm gonna get a little bit of
that cheese
there we go
just slap that on
as sonic the hedgehog says
when he's about to suck
on bobby's fat balls
down the hatch
that's a good
oh my god
the last tortilla slap that on
there like bobby smack socks ass
and dump a little of that delicious
cream corn out
come the up
come on
i don't even got a
spoon
this it is ass
guys like dripping onto the floor and
what the we're moving on from this
i can't do this sup everyone 1005
is here and he's back with the video as
you can see i walked cleaned up my
workstation unfortunately our last
attempt at the taco was a complete and
massive dump it was a pill so
instead of making what i was usually
going oh is he going to make we're going
to do some experimenting with what we
got and we're going to be using what we
have left that we did not use so put
that on there
i guess it's gonna be another dessert
taco cause
i'm out look now we got some
we got some clover valley grape jelly to
represent cream queen lena and some
cover
clover valley strawberry preserve so
we're gonna get
we're gonna get an equal amount of each
one
and then just slap that onto the taco
and that that that's pretty much it
i mean i can't really do what i was
gonna do because it was gonna involve
butter
mustard it was gonna involve some of
this
popcorn that store i i mean i got from
like my local theater and
i'll just go ahead and
i'll go ahead and use some of that
because i
i brought it down here so
that's pretty much it
that's pretty much the last taco so
blades everyone